Two drops in each ear twice a day.
We're gonna fix you right up, kid.
Shouldn't Lisbon
have called by now?
She said she would call
when there was a break in the case.
- I mean, maybe there wasn't one.
- I'm gonna call her anyway.
- You're such a worrier.
- Can you take her?
- Yeah.
- No, I'm not!
Except for when there's things
to worry about.
- "Hello?"
- Hey, it's Rigsby. Any news?
I was gonna call you
from the car.
SFPD is sending
the case over to us.
- Hey, they got the case from SFPD.
- Oh, that's great.
That's great.
How'd you convince them?
When you're FBI, people
tend to give you what you want.
- Had they developed any leads?
- Not really.
They agree that whoever murdered
Laroche and Ardiles Bugged our phones.
It's probably somebody we arrested
at the CBI someone holding a grudge.
I'm putting together a list.
I'll keep you posted.
Okay. That's great.
I'll talk to you soon.
- Wayne?
- Coming.
Can you give her drops
while I get her bath started?
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Thanks.
Go see daddy.
Come on.
There we go.
Okay.
All righty.
Let's see what we got.
Grace?
All righty, Kiddo.
This won't hurt a bit.
At least I think it won't.
No!
Wayne!
Are you all right?!
Wayne, is she hurt?
Is she hurt?
She's okay. She's okay.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- She's okay.
We're okay.
And if she has trouble falling asleep
try taking her for a ride in the car.
That usually puts her right out.
Thanks. I'll call you later.
Maddy's gonna be fine
with your aunt.
I know.
And Ben's gonna be fine
with his mother.
- They're both gonna be just fine.
- Sure.
Hey, come on.
Hey.
Welcome to Austin.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- We're okay, considering.
- You settled into your motel?
- Yeah.
Well, we heard back from the crime techs
in San Francisco.
It looks like the intruder
got into your house
through a basement window
that wasn't on your alarm system.
Did forensics find anything?
No, ballistics ran the casings
that were recovered
from the crime scene.
- There weren't any matches.
- Any eyewitnesses?
People heard shots,
but nobody saw anything.
Come on. We're just about
to start the briefing.
Hey. We're gonna get this guy.
Come on.
We believe the assailant
is the same person
that killed attorney Osvaldo Ardiles
and former California Bureau
of Investigation agent J.J. Laroche.
Now, in your packets you'll find
a preliminary list of suspects.
Some are still incarcerated
but it's possible he's orchestrating
this from prison.
Now, there are 12 names,
so we have our work cut out for us.
Acquaint yourselves
with the case files.
I'll be assigning individual suspects
for you to investigate
later this morning.
Thank you.
- Good to see you, guys.
- Yeah, you, too.
Hey.
- How you doing?
- All right.
Just got word that the FBI
has officially hired you
as consultants for the case.
You're the ones who first found out
we were being tracked.
You know this case
better than anybody.
Don't worry.
We'll figure out who it is.
Not anytime soon,
the way you're going about this.
12 suspects?
I had Wylie run the suspects
through the Vicap database.
Those are the ones
that were flagged.
What's their connection
to Ardiles?
Well, he was involved
in all their prosecutions.
Well, that's fine and Dandy,
but we're the ones that caught them
and questioned them
and we certainly know them
better than any database.
- What do you think we should do?
- I think we should trust our instincts.
- You mean take a wild guess.
- 80% of the time
a detective's first guess is right.
You just made that up.
And you knew that
because your instincts told you.
Now, come on.
Everyone, pick a photo.
- Whoever looks right.
- John Hutten, the bank robber.
He's smart, determined.
I could see him
trying something like this.
Yeah, you have a hunch.
Grace, don't be shy.
I'll go with Donny Culpepper.
He's a professional criminal
implicated in several murders.
This wouldn't be a stretch.
- Cho, you know you want to.
- Tommy Volker.
A sociopath if ever there was one.
Lisbon?
I don't know. Richard Haibach?
Linus Wagner, maybe.
The pedophile
and the homicidal shrink.
Excellent choices.
Now we have
a set of suspects.
Okay, we'll go with those five.
I'll have my agents
work the other seven.
To start, we need to know
who's in prison
who's out, and who
they've talked to recently.
Yes, well, that's not really
my sort of thing
so if you need any more help,
I'll be on my couch.
I need some help.
- Hi. Agent Fischer.
- Oh, hey.
I want you to know that everyone here
is 100% behind this investigation.
- We appreciate that.
- Thank you.
But since there's nothing for you
to do here I'm stealing you.
We've got another case.
No rest for the wicked.
Where did the wheel of death
stop today?
Bradley, Texas, an hour west.
A body was found this morning
on a fracking site.
"A worker discovered the body
in a wastewater pit."
"The victim's name is Dan Becker.
He's a local rancher..."
"Small-time, 50 acres or so."
"Couple of months ago,
he brought a lawsuit"
against a regional energy
company called Millman oil.
They're the Frackers?
Yeah, they've been developing frack sites
for the past couple of years.
The one where the body was found
is leased federal land.
That's why we caught the case.
Becker sued because he claimed
the company polluted
his ranch's groundwater.
An anti-Fracker found dead on the site
of the company he just sued.
That's murder gold.
Well, we don't know
the company's involved.
We shouldn't leap
to any conclusions.
Of course we should.
That way, it'll go a little quicker.
Sheriff says the coroner
took the body about an hour ago.
Oh, good.
Seen enough of those.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Hi, there.
I'm FBI agent Fischer.
This is my colleague, Patrick Jane.
We'd like to ask you a few questions
about Dan Becker's murder.
Just... just you.
The rest of you can go home.
- No, they can't.
- Yes, they can.
They just work here.
He's in charge.
Well, stay close.
We'll get to you in a minute.
- What makes you say I'm in charge?
- Your snakeskin boots
your nice, stiff black jeans.
Shiny belt buckle...
That air of command
that you have about you.
Well, I'm Jason Kern,
chief operating officer.
Well, you make the tough
decisions around here.
Who to fire, who to hire,
who to bribe.
Well, I wish I could do that.
Boy, that'd make my job easier,
wouldn't it?
No need to be so coy.
You're big oil.
You can do whatever you want, right?
Well, you're a character, aren't you?
So, why do you think
this was murder?
The coroner says the likely cause of death
was a blow to the head.
So it's murder, or he, uh...
fell and hit his head.
Be that as it may, we'll assist
your investigation any way we can.
Because we are not big oil, sir.
We're a regional company.
We're part of the communities
we work in.
When we succeed, they thrive.
Something is not thriving.
Yeah, our equipment
keeps shutting down.
Started right after those yahoos
protested at our offices yesterday.
What yahoos would that be?
Group that calls itself
the cooperative.
They're anti-corporate
"hacktivists"
who spread mischief
over the internet.
We think they're interfering
with the computer
that runs
the hydraulic pumps.
Maybe you should be talking
to them about Becker.
You think
an anti-corporate group
was responsible for the murder
of an anti-Fracker?
Ma'am, all I know is the cooperative
likes a grand gesture
and they don't care who they hurt
to stop the corporate agenda.
Now, would they kill a man
and try to blame us for it?
I wouldn't put it past them.
Look, I'm afraid I got my hands
full just now, all right?
You have more questions,
you all come by the office.
It'll be easier to chat there.
All right, guys.
What's... what's going on here?
Folksy.
Yeah, let's go talk to Becker's family
see what they have to say.
Okeydokey, ma'am.
Well, that's one suspect
eliminated.
Linus Wagner's been
in solitary confinement
for the past five months.
You can take Culpepper
off the list.
He got married
and moved to Venezuela.
He hasn't been back in the states
in over a year.
So who do you like now?
I keep on coming back
to Haibach.
He was on Jane's fake Red John list.
Kirkland tortured and nearly killed him.
I'd hold a grudge.
Does he have an alibi?
I have a call
Into his office in Denver.
I got something.
John Hutten's out of prison.
Apparently he's on work release.
His new address is in Houston.
That's two hours from here.
But Hutten's a bank robber.
He's not a killer.
Well, whoever attacked the house
bypassed the security system
- and that took planning.
- That sounds like Hutten.
I'll go talk to him. Sure.
- Mind if I come with?
- Can I drive?
- No.
Why not?
Consultants don't drive.
It's policy.
- Whose?
- Mine.
Oh, come on.
- Mrs. Becker?
- No.
I'm... I'm Susan...
Susan Fitzgerald.
I'm a family friend.
But Molly's here somewhere.
I'm agent Fischer with the FBI.
This is Patrick Jane.
- May we come in?
- Of course, yes.
This is my husband, Emmett.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Where is the kitchen?
- It's right through there.
- Thank you.
They're with the FBI.
- How long did you two know Dan?
- Oh, since he was a kid.
We've always been close.
That's what
makes this so hard.
- Who are you?
- I'm Patrick Jane.
I'm with the FBI.
You... you must be Molly.
Sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
I wouldn't fill that in the tap.
Use the bottled water.
Groundwater's full of methane.
Been that way almost a year.
- Fracking.
- Yeah.
Wonderful, isn't it?
Killed off a bunch of our cattle, too.
Well, I can see
why Dan wanted to sue.
Dan was gonna win that lawsuit,
come hell or high water.
You thought the suit
was a bad idea?
I just didn't see the point.
Nobody's gonna testify
against Millman oil.
They make everybody
too much money.
And that lawsuit did not make
Dan very popular in town
- I'll tell you that much.
- There were other reasons, though.
- Weren't there?
- We could've sold instead of suing.
We need the money.
And Dan could barely work
with his hurt back.
And then Dan couldn't pass the ranch
on to his son.
Nathaniel.
He's on his way home
from a camping trip.
It meant a lot to Dan
that his son would get the land
that he got
from his father, and...
he was stubborn.
Now there's nothing
stopping you.
You gonna sell?
Just as soon as I can.
And what do you think
about Millman oil?
- Well...
- I'll say it.
They saved this town.
It was dying.
They brought it back to life.
So you don't think they had
anything to do with Dan's death?
- No! No. No way.
- You're a fool, Fitzgerald.
Oh, man.
- And who are you?
- Bryce Kendrick.
Me and Danny known each other
since we was kids.
I knew him better than anybody.
And I wouldn't trust these two idiots.
Millman oil...
- They're behind this.
- Come on, Bryce.
That company is ruining this town.
Police, politicians...
They ain't lifting a finger
because they're bought off.
Here we go again.
Nobody dares cross them.
Dan tried. Hmm?
Look what happened to him.
They didn't kill Dan.
That's crazy.
Only reason
you're saying that, Emmett...
Is 'cause
you're in bed with them.
Yeah, by the way,
they sold their fracking rights
quick as they could.
Money whores, the both of them.
You would've done
the same thing
if you had any land
worth selling.
Yeah.
- You smug son of a bitch.
- Hey!
It's all right, everyone.
- Yeah.
- It's under control.
I'm cool. I'm cool.
Sorry.
Now, why are you so convinced
that Millman oil killed Dan?
About a couple of weeks ago
they sent a bunch of thugs out here
to rough him up
Hurt him bad.
Busted up his back.
They wanted old Danny
to drop his lawsuit.
- Said he wouldn't do it.
- I didn't see a police report.
He didn't go to the police.
I told you...
Everyone in this town
is on their payroll.
- Did Dan know who ordered the attack?
- He had his suspicions, yeah.
Yeah, there was someone
behind the payoffs
and the threats and...
some bigwig
with Millman oil.
- Which bigwig?
- Danny didn't know.
But it was one of them.
- Hi.
Can I help you?
FBI, ma'am.
We're looking for John Hutten.
Johnny?
Johnny, FBI's here.
It's okay, darling.
Go ahead.
Sorry I can't stay.
- See you Wednesday afternoon, okay?
- Yeah. Have a good flight.
I remember you guys
from California.
FBI, huh?
That's a step up.
- What are you doing out of prison?
- Spending time with my wife.
She's a good woman.
I enjoy domestic life.
How did you
get out so soon?
Behaved myself.
They let me go.
Prison overcrowding...
it's a problem.
You been to San Francisco recently?
- Why?
- Answer the question.
I don't know that I remember.
Maybe it'll come to you
back at our office.
- Let's go.
- That's an excellent idea.
I've been wanting
to get out of the house.
Yeah. We've got Hutten.
We'll be back in a couple hours.
- Ready?
- One second.
All right. Let's go.
FBI! Hands where I can see them!
Hey, take it easy!
I'm FBI, too!
Kimball Cho.
This is Wayne Rigsby.
It's cool.
I'm Miller,
Houston bank robbery division.
What the hell
are you doing with Hutten?
We're taking him in
for questioning.
No, you can't do that.
- And why not?
- Why not?
Because he works for me.
Hutten's been working for my team
for the past year
to take down bank-robbery rings.
That's why they let him out early.
Did I not mention that?
He's also a suspect
in two homicides.
Homicides?
You're kidding. When?
Within the last two weeks
both in San Francisco.
- Has Hutten been there recently?
- San Jose.
We had an operation there.
Just got back yesterday.
But you got the wrong guy.
San Jose's an hour
from my house.
- He could've done this.
- Yeah.
No, see,
I think miller would've known.
Do you see that dot?
That's Hutten. He wears
an ankle-monitoring device.
I know where he is at all times.
That's how I knew he left the house,
for God's sake.
He's not your killer.
- We're done here, aren't we?
- Yeah. Yeah, we are.
Best of luck, guys.
- You from the FBI?
- Yes.
Samuel Millman.
I own this place.
- Welcome, welcome.
- Agent Kim Fischer.
- Patrick Jane.
- Jane.
Jason told me about you.
Maybe you agree with what
these people did to my company.
But come on.
I'll show you something there.
"Stop fracking now!"
They call themselves the cooperative
whatever the hell that means.
The music is some kind
of calling card.
You know, in my day, if you had
a problem with someone
you would just tell them
face-to-face
none of this
computer-hacking nonsense...
Not that I pretend to understand
any of it.
Are you looking into the possibility
that they killed that poor man, Becker?
Your Mr. Kern asked
exactly the same thing.
- It's a valid theory.
- Yeah, perhaps.
But the cooperative
is an online activist group.
Murder is a different thing.
Well, look at that.
You speak of the devil,
and he shall appear.
Mr. Jane, Ms. Fischer.
To what do we owe
the pleasure?
Did either of you deal directly
with Dan Becker?
Not me. In the last few years
I've taken a step back
from the day-to-day operations.
The company shifted its focus
to our fracking activities.
That's my area of expertise.
Oh, so you would've been the one
who ordered the assault on Becker.
That's funny. Yeah.
No, there have been
no assaults ordered
or anything like that.
You'd think a man in your position
would be a better liar.
Mr. Jane, we're not an evil company.
- You truly believe that, don't you?
- Of course I do!
Look, we're the victims here.
What the hell?
What...
What's going on here?
- Jason?
- I don't know.
"This is the cooperative."
"Millman oil has committed
its latest crime..."
"The murder of a man
named Dan Becker."
"This will not go unpunished."
"The cooperative
will be listening."
will be watching."
"And we will not rest
until justice is served."
Well, that was weird.
And it's obvious they think Millman oil's
behind this but why?
You said that the cooperative
hacked into their office.
Maybe they found something
to connect them to the murder.
So why not come to us with it?
These kind of groups aren't
what you'd call "FBI friendly."
We're investigating half of them
for cybercrimes.
So how do we find out
what the cooperative knows?
You could start
with whoever made that video.
- Can you track him down, Wylie?
- Yeah, I can try.
Let me know
if you find anything.
Well, I heard one
of your suspects didn't pan out.
Hutten? Big bust.
We only have a few more names
on the list.
We're running low.
Lisbon.
I need to see you
in my office.
Agent Lisbon, Laura Dubin...
Attorney for Richard Haibach.
Mr. Haibach is in Denver
but I'm going to conference him in.
Hello, Richard. I'm here
with agents Abbott and Lisbon.
- "You damn people are..."
- One moment, Richard, please.
Agent Abbott, did you know agent Lisbon
contacted Mr. Haibach's employer
to ask about his whereabouts
During Osvaldo Ardiles' murder?
I was not aware of that.
For the record
Mr. Haibach was at a dinner
with two coworkers.
"I want to know what justification you have
for endangering my career!"
This is an active investigation.
I'm not at liberty to say more.
Which means you have nothing to say.
Agent Abbott
my client has suffered enough
at the hands of agent Lisbon.
If you continue to do this
we will have no choice but to sue.
That won't be necessary.
Good.
I may consider the investigation
into Mr. Haibach closed?
You may.
"I want an apology from her
from agent Lisbon's lips!"
Mr. Haibach, I am very sorry
if I've caused you any inconvenience.
- It won't happen again.
- "It better not!"
Agents.
- Please, sir, you can't drop this.
- We're not.
There's something off
about that man.
I want you to put a surveillance
team together
but just give it 24 hours
before you do.
I want him to think
that he's off the hook.
Yes, sir.
Okay, buddy.
I'll see you soon.
I love you.
- How's Ben?
- He's fine.
Please tell me
you have some good news.
Wish I did.
Volker's in federal lockup
so I had the prison check his
communications for the last six months.
There's nothing there.
Anything on the other
seven suspects?
A few leads.
No breakthroughs.
Which leaves us with Haibach
who we have nothing on.
Take a break.
Get something to eat.
Yeah. Okay. Thanks.
Fudge!
Of course he used an anonymizing
proxy server.
Why would you want
to make my life easy?
Was I talking out loud?
No problem.
I'm Grace.
I'm Wylie. Sorry if I disturbed you.
Excuse me.
Want some help?
Ever try cracking a daisy-chained
anonymizing proxy server?
Sure. What's going on?
Well, uh, a cooperative member
posted a video earlier today.
I'm looking for the upload location.
Problem is, he routed it
through 70 different servers.
Well, a lot of times these guys use public
computers to avoid detection.
I checked that...
20 of the servers are public locations.
Did you unlock
the video's file attributes?
I know some good
forensic-decryption software.
- Dorsey, maybe?
- McClaren. It's faster.
Here we go...
He uploaded the video today
at about 5:00 p.m.
Interesting.
He posted dozens of videos
all of them uploaded between
5:00 p.m. and midnight.
Any of the public locations
open late?
Wylie says our guy's been
uploading videos from this lab
almost every night
between 5:00 and midnight.
It's 9:00 now, so he may be here.
Yeah.
But it could be anyone.
It's him.
Are you sure?
Yeah, look at his eyes...
all squirrelly.
Don't you think?
Excuse me, sir?
FBI. I need to ask you
a few questions, please.
Fischer.
I lied. It's him.
Sir...
Wa... FBI. Stop!
- Hey, hey!
- What are you doing?!
- Sorry.
- Don't do that!
- Sorry. Shh.
- Leave him alone!
Ethan Zorn.
Enrolled at U.T.
at the age of 14
dropped out
after one semester.
Arrested a year later
for hacking into Nasa.
I assume
you have a point.
I don't think that you are a run-of-the-mill
cooperative type.
If I had to take a guess...
I would say that you are
the one in charge.
You believe that Millman oil
is responsible for Dan Becker's death.
- Why?
- Well, call it a hunch.
I don't think you understand,
Mr. Zorn.
The federal government
doesn't treat cybercrimes lightly.
Conspiracy to engage in hacking
carries a 10-year sentence.
Now, you may be tough
behind a computer
but in a cellblock...
The... the cooperative
has an e-mail account
where whistle-blowers
can get in touch.
Dan sent a note regarding
his troubled lawsuit.
- He wanted my help.
- Your help for what?
He heard a rumor
that an executive at Millman oil
kept a black book of names...
all the people he'd paid off.
Dan wanted that book.
An executive...
Jason Kern.
Exactly.
So, together, Dan and I hatched a plan.
I would organize a protest
at the front of the building.
That would distract security
and Dan would be able to break
into kern's office in the back.
We staged it on a Sunday
so nobody would be in the office.
Okay, what about the alarms,
the locks, the cameras?
A joke for someone
with my skills.
I hacked the alarm systems,
and I gave Dan a list of Jason kern's
possible pass-code combinations
if needed.
Most people are very predictable
in their choices.
Well, something didn't go
according to plan.
Uh, either Dan
was discovered in the act
or he was tracked down
afterwards.
All I know for sure is that I never heard
from him again.
The tanker would then cost
a million bucks.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Excuse me?
- Your secretary's out to lunch.
Hope you don't mind
we let ourselves in.
What are you doing here?
Why didn't you tell us that Dan Becker
broke into your office?
- Because he didn't.
- Oh, yes, he did.
And he searched the place
until he found your safe.
Safe.
And he opened it and he stole
your little black book of names.
Jason, what are they talking about?
Mr. Kern here has been bribing
residents and city officials
to keep them from testifying
against your company.
This is ridiculous.
All right, I don't have
a black book, and even if I did
how did Becker get into my safe
without a combination?
Well, he did.
You obviously had a very
simple code... your birth date?
- How d...
- Yes.
Was anything else taken,
aside from the book?
- No.
- That was a yes.
- The book and what else?
- Nothing was taken, all right?
No black book, no nothing!
All right, look, you know what?
I'm sorry, but you people need to leave.
We just have a few more questions.
Then I'm gonna have
to bring in our lawyers.
Exactly.
- Oh, this is interesting.
- What?
Look at the indentation
on the carpet.
Someone has moved
this file-cabinet thing
when they were searching
for the safe.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
There was no break-in!
We're done here.
So, you think Dan
took something else.
- Like what?
- I don't know.
Money, maybe.
Kern would need a slush fund.
I mean, he's not paying
people off with checks.
I need to make a stop
on the way back.
- Where are we going?
- Talk to Dan's friends.
- Why?
- Patience.
Ah, everyone is here.
Please, come on in.
Take a seat.
Thank you.
There's been a very interesting
development in the case.
I'm gonna need you all to pay
very careful attention.
Agent Fischer, if you would.
Thank you.
Now, does this song
mean something to any of you?
"London bridge is falling down"?
It's a nursery rhyme, isn't it?
Anything else?
Bryce?
Susan?
Molly?
This is why you brought us here?
Thank you for your time.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Are you gonna tell me
what this is about?
Nope.
I want to talk to Hutten again.
- No.
- Just hear me out.
He's wearing a monitoring device.
I checked in with miller's unit
and they say that Hutten hasn't
left the house in 14 hours.
- And...
- That doesn't seem strange at all?
Not necessarily.
I also tried to call Hutten.
No answer.
Look, maybe it's nothing
but we don't have any other leads.
What do we have to lose?
Just so you know,
this is a waste of time.
You sure Hutten's home?
He's here.
He's probably just sleeping.
John, open up!
- You got a key?
- No, just wait.
Excuse me.
- What the hell are you doing?!
- Sorry.
You can't go in there!
He's not upstairs.
I'll call in a bolo.
This doesn't make any sense.
His monitor says that he's right here.
Yeah.
'Cause he modified his cellphone
to give out the same signal
as the ankle monitor.
You leave it on, everybody
thinks he's still home.
Yep. I'm guessing he's gone.
Thanks, Cho. Got it.
I just got off the phone
with Hutten's wife.
She's been in San Diego
for two days
and has no idea
where her husband is.
Any luck?
Cho just got a hit
on the bolo.
A convenience-store tenant
saw Hutten 20 minutes ago.
He left traveling west
in a blue jeep.
Okay. I've got the nearest
traffic-light camera.
There it is.
He turned left on Hampton.
I'll start pulling more footage.
Maybe I can track where he's headed.
All righty.
Wylie. You got five minutes
to help catch a killer?
- Yes. Absolutely.
- Good.
How much can you really learn
about someone on the internet...
- I mean, intimate details?
- You'd be surprised.
Of course, if you have a court order
for phone records
and credit-card transactions
you can find a lot more.
- Do we have a court order?
- Would I be asking if we didn't?
"Everything's going
according to plan."
"Agent Collins is at his house,
siphoning his gas."
"Okay, he's headed out now."
All right. It's working.
He pulled into the gas station.
- Are we all set on your end?
- "All set. Good to go."
All right.
Hey, man, what's wrong
with these radios, huh?
Don't know. Just came on.
"Hello, Bryce."
"Yeah, you.
I'm talking to you, Bryce."
Hello?
"This is the cooperative."
"Did you really think you were
gonna get away with it?"
What?
What the hell's going on?
"Oh, come on.
We know you killed Dan Becker."
No, I did not.
I would never hurt Dan.
"We know you did it,
and now we know why."
"You helped Dan break into
Jason Kern's office"
"but you didn't just find
the black book, did you?"
"No, you wouldn't murder
Dan for that."
"You found kern's slush fund."
"You killed Dan so you could have
the money for yourself."
No, I didn't.
Don't worry.
We're not turning you in.
The cooperative
makes its own justice.
"You're not gonna get away
with this, Bryce."
What are you gonna do?
Well, we know where you hid
the money, and we took it.
- You couldn't possibly know that.
- We know everything, Bryce.
Don't believe us?
Today for lunch you ordered
a ham and cheese
with chips and a drink.
"Last week,
you saw a dermatologist"
"for a reoccurring case
of athlete's foot."
Two months ago,
you were fired
after a coworker accused you
of sexual harassment.
Now do you believe me?
How could you
possibly know that?
I told you...
we know everything
and we made sure you wouldn't
profit from Dan Becker's death.
Goodbye, Bryce.
Hello?
What do you got there, Bryce?
Now, we know you helped Dan.
He had a bad back.
He couldn't have moved
that file cabinet by himself.
Anybody could've helped him.
Why me?
Jane could tell you were
the only one
who knew what "London bridge
is falling down" really meant.
You heard the cooperative playing it
during the break-in, didn't you?
Yeah, I helped Dan.
He wanted backup
in case something went wrong.
Found the safe in Kern's office.
Cash was in it,
along with the black book.
$100,000, man...
- But Dan didn't want the money?
- No.
Thought it would make him a thief.
But I didn't.
I needed that money.
I deserved that money.
Everybody else is getting rich, huh?
Why couldn't I have a little?
"Figured what Dan didn't know
wouldn't hurt him."
Let's get out of here.
"Stop fracking now!"
So, what went wrong?
Bad luck, I guess.
Thanks, man.
Nice work.
- What the hell is this?!
- Hey, hey, wait a minute, Dan!
Let me explain!
We're not keeping the money.
That's not what
we were supposed to do.
We deserve it, Dan!
They are profiting
off of our land!
Doesn't make it right.
I'm giving it back.
The hell you are.
Hey.
"Ah, he just wasn't breathing."
"And, uh..."
I didn't know what to do.
So you dumped the body
on Millman oil property.
I figured if anybody deserved
to get in trouble, it was them.
But I never meant
to hurt Dan.
Mr. Kern.
It's a very detailed book.
Thank you for this.
We have a lot to talk about, don't we?
Oh, this'll be tied up in court
for years, and you know it.
We have some
very good lawyers.
They won't be working for you.
You're fired.
Samuel, we can beat this.
I'm done with your lies, Jason.
- Get him out of my sight.
- Samuel, wait.
Samuel!
Hold on. Back up.
Blue jeep.
Hey.
FBI, ma'am.
All right.
Aw, man.
Any chance you guys
can come back in a half an hour?
He's been hacking
the ankle monitor
so he can bang his girlfriend
without his wife knowing.
the mistress says she visited Hutten
last Thursday in San Jose
the same day Ardiles died.
They were in a hotel
the whole time.
It checks out.
Hutten's not our guy.
So, where are we
on Haibach?
His surveillance detail should be up.
Let me call.
- "Hello?"
- Agent burns, hi.
This is agent Lisbon in Austin.
- Anything to report?
- "No. We got nothing."
"Haven't seen the guy all night."
All right, well, keep me updated.
We got nothing.
- I could use a drink.
- I'm in.
- We should grab Jane.
- Count me out.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm beat.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
- All right, Lisbon.
- Good night. Okay.
Hey. I fell asleep.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to check in.
I'm out having
a drink with the guys.
- What happened with Hutten?
- It's not him. I'll explain later.
You go back to bed.
- You having fun?
- Yeah. Yeah, I am.
- I'm glad. It's good for you.
- Thank you.
I love you, babe.
You know that, right?
I love you, too.
- Okay, I'll see you soon.
- Good night.